var questions = [
	{
		question:
			"During the evacuation of Gallipoli, who did ANZAC fought against?",
		choices: ["German army", "Japanese army", "Turkish army", "Italian army"],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
	{
		question:
			"In the Queenslander Pictorial; Fighting lines east and west, which country’s soldiers built villas at the front of battlefields. The villas consist of entrance to the refuge from bombs and shells",
		choices: ["Australia", "France", "Great Britain", "Germany"],
		correctAnswer: 1
	},
	{
		question:
			"Which country’s prisoners were captive by the Germans in the Göttingen Camp?",
		choices: ["France", "Australia", "Great Britain", "Austria"],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
	{
		question:
			"During the World War 1, soldiers from various different countries had made use of animals. The Red Cross organization was famous for using these types of animals to save wounded in France. Which were they?",
		choices: ["Pigeons", "Elephants", "Horses", "Dogs"],
		correctAnswer: 3
	},
	{
		question:
			"In the picture of Hun’s work and the Balkan Expedition, you can see houses destroyed by bombs which killed two innocent children and English soldiers marching. Which district did this tragedy happened in?",
		choices: ["London", "Birmingham", "Manchester", "Dover"],
		correctAnswer: 0
	},
	{
		question:
			"World War 1 was one of the global tragedies that happened from which year to which year?",
		choices: ["1935 to 1938", "1939 to 1945", "1914 to 1918", "1861 to 1865"],
		correctAnswer: 2
	},
	{
		question:
			"World War 1 took place in vast areas of Europe, but also took place in other continents. This continent also had many colonized countries by European countries. Which continent was it?",
		choices: ["North America", "Africa", "Asia", "South America"],
		correctAnswer: 1
	},
	{
		question:
			"A new type of weapons was introduced and used in World War 1. Which was it?",
		choices: ["Nuclear", "Biological", "Cyber", "Chemical"],
		correctAnswer: 3
	},
	{
		question:
			"Which of the following countries did not participate in World War 1?",
		choices: ["Australia", "UK", "USA", "Switzerland"],
		correctAnswer: 3
	},
	{
		question:
			"Which of the following countries has the highest number of soldiers killed in the first World War?",
		choices: ["Australia", "Germany", "France", "Switzerland"],
		correctAnswer: 1
	}
];
